[Music]
let me show you a neat little trick that
you can use in the data analysis feature
in business
Central you probably already know that
you can filter your Fields here in the
analysis filter
menu but did you know that you can also
filter your totals just like in normal
reports in business Central
this is how that is done let's this is
a account receivables report you can see
my customers down here and I have some
remaining different sums of remaining
amounts and I would like to filter away
any rows or data here where the amount
is greater where the I want to remove
all the zero amounts so what I do here
is simply on the on this aggregated or
totaled um
column I can filter here and I can say
greater than
zero there you go and voila now you have
filtered on totals you can then save
this as part of your data analysis
definition